Come on, everybody
up! Hands in the air!
You back there, pull that
shade. And don't try it!
All right, pull those
curtain back there.
Everybody, except the tellers,
put your hands in the air, walk
quickly to the center of the room.
Hands in the air!
Come on, do it right now!
You tell them! One, two.
- Get up there!
- Three. Take three steps back.
Stick your hands in the
top of your pants and skirts.
You stay right there.
Hello, Becky. Long time no see.
All right, I want everything in those
four drawers and the safe behind you.
Now!
Cool.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't try it, my friend.
Come on, Willie, let's go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Stay out of it.
- On the floor!
- What the hell's going on?
So, what have you been doing
with yourself these days, Willie?
I'm a farmer. What do you think?
Yeah?
So, what's this Ben Franklin
doing on the floor mat
in the back seat of your car?
You're getting sloppy in your old age.
Look, I don't know what
you're talking about. I swear it.
Seems like I heard
those exact same words
the last time you knocked
off the Willow Springs Bank.
Who's your partner, Willie?
I didn't do it, damn
it! Easy. Come on.
Detective?
- Yeah, you didn't do it.
- Ugh.
- Save your breath.
- Ben...
- I don't wanna hear it.
- I didn't do it this time.
Save your one call to
phone somebody who cares.
- I've been set up.
- One time, just one time,
I'd like to walk in this room
and hear somebody say,
"I did it. I wasn't framed. I wasn't at
the wrong place at the wrong time.
I did it. I'm sorry I did it and I'm
ready to pay the consequences."
- Just once.
- Just give me one minute.
That's all I'm asking.
Ben, you haven't
seen me in six years.
I'm a changed man.
I realize I said the same thing to
you the last time you defended me.
- For robbing the same bank.
And for telling the
people in that same bank
to do exactly what you told the
people to do in the bank six years ago.
- Ben, I...
- Willie, how many bank robbers
do you think there are
that yell at the tellers
to put their hands
in their pants?
I served my time. I've been doing
community service ever since.
I've been a model citizen, Ben.
Burn me once, shame on you.
Burn me twice, shame on me.
Let me guess. You
got no alibi, right?
Here's a list of good lawyers.
Ben, you more than anyone
else know how good I was.
So ask yourself this:
Would I ever commit a
robbery using my own car?
Would I ever be so absent-minded
as to leave a stray $100 bill
just lying around in
the back seat of my car?
Would I ever leave a ski
mask I'd just used in a heist
in plain view, in
my own backyard?
You know what the
answer is to that, Ben.
How long have you
been working as a teller
- at the Willow Spring Bank?
- Almost nine years.
So you were working there
the last time it was robbed
by the defendant and
his partner six years ago?
Yes, I was.
Do you remember the
events of that robbery?
Vividly.
Mr. Roach and his partner walked
out of the bathroom wearing ski masks.
Then they told everybody
in the main area of the bank
to congregate in a circle.
Then Mr. Roach came
over to my teller window.
What did he instruct you to do?
Well, he had all of the other
tellers take three steps backwards
and place their hands inside
their pants or their skirts.
Inside their pants?
Yeah, it was such a bizarre request.
That's why I remember it so well.
Then he had me collect all the
money from the tellers' drawers,
as well as from the safe.
Ms. Schraven, was there
anything about this latest robbery
that was similar to
the one six years ago?
They were identical.
The ski masks, the congregating
of people in the center of the room.
He even told the tellers to take
exactly three steps backwards
and place their hands
inside their belts.
Was there anything
different about this robbery
from the one that
happened six years ago?
Yes. When the bank robber
approached me this time,
he smiled and he said, "Hello,
Becky. Long time no see."
He was so arrogant.
Did you recognize that voice?
I'd recognize that voice
with my eyes closed.
It was the defendant's.
Well, when I saw them running
out of the bank with their ski masks,
I knew what had happened.
And then what did
you do, Mr. Golding?
Well, I started after them but
one man pointed his gun at me.
Do you remember which
hand he was holding his gun in?
Oh, yeah. It was his left hand.
It would be safe to presume that
the man pointing the gun at you
- was left-handed. Yeah. Mm-hm.
Mr. Golding, did you hear any words
exchanged between the bank robbers?
Oh, yeah.
After the first man drew his
gun, the second man yelled,
"Come on, Willie,
let's get out of here."
"Come on, Willie"? You're
certain that's the name you heard?
Oh, yeah. I heard it. I
heard it loud and clear.
That's all.
Mr. Matlock?
No questions, Your Honor.
Then this court stands in
recess until 9:30 Thursday.
Someone did me up good.
If someone did you up,
Willie, they did you up great.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hello.
- Uh, you Ben Matlick?
- No, it's Matlock.
No, no, I'm not him. But maybe
I can help you with something.
I don't want your help.
Well, what is it you wanted
to see Mr. Matlock about?
Uh, why don't you get
Mr. Matlock and I'll tell him?
Mr. Matlock is busy.
- Who's here?
- Some kid. I don't know. Whoa, whoa!
My name's Matt and
get your hands off of me.
What's going on?
Did you wanna
talk to me, uh, Matt?
Uh, yeah, but how about in
private? I don't want him to hear.
Oh.
- How about some peanut butter?
- Uh, how about a cigarette?
How about some peanut butter?
- That's all I get?
- That's all I got for you.
I can prove Willie Roach didn't
rob the bank at Willow Springs.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I was there when
the robbers drove off.
What do you want?
You got anything sweet?
- I'm listening.
- Well, I ain't talking. Not yet.
Excuse me?
We need to make... We
need to make an arrangement.
What kind of arrangement?
I'll tell you everything you need
to know to get Willie Roach off
if you promise to defend my dad.
He just got busted
for stealing cars.
You eat my peanut butter, my chips,
drink my milk and then blackmail me?
Dad always says
life wasn't fair.
Look where it got him.
How do I know that
you were at the bank?
Their car was blue,
it was parked at the first meter
from the driveway of the bank.
And when they drove off, their
bumper clipped the parking meter
as they went away.
So, what do you
say? We got a deal?
Deal.
I am so grateful that you're
helping me out here, Mr. Matlock.
- Well, you can, uh, thank your son.
- Yeah.
- Good old Matty.
- Yeah, good old Matty.
He says you tend
bar for a living.
Yeah. At Plato's Bar and Grill.
Well, what were you
doing at that chop shop
when the police
found those cars?
It's not a chop shop,
Mr. Matlock. It's a body shop.
And Mark Lipton has been a
friend of mine since I was a kid.
- Who's Mark Lipton?
- He's the owner.
So, uh, you didn't
steal any of those cars
the police found at
your friend's body shop?
No, of course not.
Explain what you were doing
with $2,000 in your pocket
and how your fingerprints got all
over the inside of that stolen Porsche
the police impounded.
The reason I had the cash
was because Mark had just
paid me back some money
I had loaned to him.
And what happened was I got
there and he was with a client.
And I was just killing time.
I saw that beautiful Porsche,
and I just wanted to see what
it would be like on the inside.
So I hopped in. Now, that's
what happened, scout's honor.
Hmm.
Did you say "scout's honor" the last
time you got busted for stealing cars?
That was a long
time ago, Mr. Matlock.
I'm a changed man.
Changed man.
I've heard that before lately.
If I hear it many more times,
I'm gonna toss my cookies.
Are you gonna take my case?
I promised your boy I would,
so I'll talk to you in a couple days.
Well, how's my dad? I
mean, did you see him?
- Is he all right?
- Okay.
- So are you gonna take his case?
- I told you I would.
Now it's your turn. What
did you see at the bank?
- Well, first you gotta put up his bail.
- Oh, okay.
- Whoa, whoa, where are you going?
- To drop your father's case.
All right, listen, you don't
have to pick up his bail.
It's just that I don't wanna
have to have him stay in jail.
You ready to talk?
Let's go in the bathroom.
- Well?
- Shh.
I saw the two bank robbers.
What do you mean, "saw"?
When both of them went back to
their car, they took off their masks.
I saw them and neither one of
those guys was Willie Roach.
You're sure?
I saw Willie Roach's picture in the
newspaper when he got arrested.
I'm positive.
Matt, if you looked at
some police mug books,
do you think you
could pick them out?
- If they're in there, I'll find them.
- Okay. I got court.
I'll set it up
for a little later.
Maybe you better go home now.
Your mother might be worried about you.
Uh, my mom is dead.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Well, where are you staying?
- Uh, at my aunt's house.
- Oh. Where is that? I'll give you a lift.
Uh, 825 Front Street.
825.
Front Street only goes
up to the 600 block.
I'm sorry, Matt, I can't
let you stay by yourself.
I'm not staying at no shelter.
Okay, for now, you
can stay with me.
- Cool.
- Okay.
- Mr. Matlock.
- Mr. Matlock, do you think
you're going to get
Roach acquitted?
I'd just as soon
not get into that.
But what about the testimony of the
teller and the parking lot attendant?
I'm not gonna get into that.
Does Willie Roach have an
alibi for the day of the robbery?
Do you think there's a
copycat robber out there?
Pete, Pete, got a second?
We got trouble.
That kid with Ben Matlock, that's
the one I saw in the parking lot.
- What did Matlock say?
- I don't know.
That kid saw both of us, Pete.
Yeah, this is Pete.
You see the news?
I raise.
So you didn't recognize
anyone in those mug shots, huh?
- No.
- That's too bad.
Are you gonna talk
or are we gonna play?
I'm gonna fold. I'm
gonna go eat my winnings.
It's five chocolate mints
to you if you wanna stay in.
It's yours.
Now that the
lightweight's gone, uh,
what do you say we
play for some real stakes?
Penny, nickel, dime?
What do you say the loser goes
and gets ice cream for the winner?
You're on.
Shuffle them up.
There you go.
I feel lucky.
How many?
- Four.
- Oh, one of a kind. Good hand.
I'm gonna take, uh...
I'm gonna take three.
Guess it's show
and tell time, huh?
Well, that's unless
you wanna raise the pot.
To what?
The loser buys ice cream
for everybody in the house.
And it's double scoops.
It's your money.
Three eights.
Three little guys with
little crowns on their heads.
Three kings? Hey, hold
on. You can't do that.
Let me tell you something, Matt.
If you're gonna play by your
own rules, even if you cheat,
there's always gonna be somebody
who does it better than you.
I'll take a double
scoop of chocolate chip.
Cliff likes vanilla.
Hey, forget the kid! Come
on, let's go! Come on!
Go, go, go!
- You all right?
- Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
So, what was Joe Ahern doing here
the night that the police arrested him?
You mean when the police knocked
down my door and handcuffed me?
Uh, yeah, whatever.
What was he doing here?
I owed him some money.
He came by to pick it up.
- Was that your 2 grand?
- Yeah.
You mind my asking why
you borrowed $2,000 from him?
Nothing in particular. Bills.
This look like a
chop shop to you?
I'm really the wrong
person to ask that.
It's infuriating. You try to
run a legitimate business...
Why don't you
leave me your card?
I'm considering filing an unlawful
arrest suit against the police.
Maybe your firm could handle it.
Why don't we
deal with that later?
Right now I just have to make sure
that Joe Ahern wasn't being paid off
for any business dealings
you might have had with him.
Look, I know you're doing your job,
but these questions, they offend me.
Believe me, you're the last
guy on earth I want to offend.
I know that.
Look, Joe's a bartender.
I run a body shop.
What kind of business
dealings could we possibly have?
We're friends, Mr. Lewis.
And that's all we are, friends.
This will just take
a couple minutes.
- Why can't I just stay in the car?
- Well, I told you.
If you're gonna take
the stand for me,
I have to know exactly where you
were when you saw the bank robbers.
- I can tell you from in here.
- Matt, we've been through that before.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Come on.
Come on.
Come on, let's
go. Let's get out.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Okay, here we go.
Hey, hey, hey, you!
- What are you doing here?
- Let's go.
- Why are you yelling at the boy?
- The boy is a thief.
I caught him four times stealing
things from cars parked in my lot.
- He's lying.
- I'm not lying.
So that's what you were doing
when you saw the robbers drive off.
You know what you've
done to Willie Roach's case?
You're no good as a witness
anymore. I can't put you on the stand.
The DA finds out you were
ripping off cars, he'll tear you apart.
I'll drop your
father's case now.
We made an arrangement.
I said I'd tell you what I knew
about the case. That was our deal.
- I lived up to my part.
- Let's go.
- Where are we going?
- To a shelter.
- I'm not going to no shelter.
- Yes...
- Hey.
- Ah.
- What are you doing?
- Pulling weeds.
Doesn't look like much fun.
It's not.
- You mad?
- Yeah.
You're mad that Matt ran away?
Why would I be mad about that?
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
- We need to talk.
- We don't need to talk.
I packed your stuff. You're
heading for the shelter.
I'm not going to a shelter.
I've been thinking
about the robbery
- and I remember something.
- What?
Well, why don't we
discuss it over coffee?
- Over milk.
- What's wrong with coffee?
You're a kid. We'll
discuss it over milk.
- Some apple pie?
- Yeah, and, uh, more milk.
I'm ready.
- Boy, are you in a bad mood.
- I'm not in a bad mood.
I just wanna know
what you remember.
First you gotta promise
you'll defend my father's case.
Starting right now, you're living
under a whole new set of rules.
You so much as lie to me
about your temperature,
I drop your father's case
and you go to juvenile hall.
- You are in a bad mood.
- Let's hear it.
You know those stickers they
have for Dynamo Rent-A-Cars?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Well, the thieves' car
was a blue Chevy Lumina.
On the window there was a
Dynamo Rental Car sticker.
It was a rental.
You gotta admit now,
that's pretty good.
So, what do you say,
can I have my room back?
Please?
Hey, Matt, what are you doing?
This person's car door was open.
I was just closing it for them.
Look, I was.
We told you not to come outside
after what happened yesterday.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
- Wanna go see your dad?
- Yeah, sounds cool.
There you go, Mr. Lewis.
- Thanks, Paul. We'll just be a minute.
- All right.
Hold on. I thought you said you
were gonna take me to see my father.
We're gonna go. We'll go.
Ever been inside
a jail cell before?
No.
Come on.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
Sit down.
- Can I please go see my dad?
- Oh, just relax. We'll go.
- You like to read?
- No.
- Like to draw?
- No. Can we please go?
Yeah, I know something you like
to do. Poke around in people's cars.
Look, I already
told you, I wasn't...
Hey, please, don't
insult me. All right?
I tell you, you are
lucky you are underage.
Because if you were 18, you got
caught breaking into someone's car
or stealing, I don't know, a hubcap, you
know, you'd end up in here for months.
- Okay. Can we go now?
- No, no, we can't go now.
Think you're bored now, Matt.
Just sitting in here day in and
day out every day with nothing to do.
And you're scared to go
out there. You know why?
Because the guys you gotta eat
with, the guys you gotta shower with,
- they're a lot tougher than you are.
- Yeah, I got it.
You don't really get
to see your friends.
You know they are allowed to
come visit you but they don't come.
They're embarrassed.
You don't really get
to watch a lot of TV.
But I tell you, the worst part is at night
when you're trying to sleep, you can't.
Because all night long there's
one or two guys just screaming
and yelling that
they wanna get out.
All right, now we
can go see your dad.
Mr. Kerr, your
foursome is on the tee
and Bridges party to follow.
Bridges party, we have
Mr. Jones to join you.
Jeff.
Yeah, Bonnie?
So, what's up?
Jeff, this is Cliff Lewis
from Ben Matlock's office.
- Oh, yeah, hi.
- Hi, how are you?
Good, good.
- Thanks, Bonnie.
- You're welcome.
- If anybody gets her, I do.
- Right. Right.
- Thanks for seeing me.
- It's no problem.
You know, I've been thinking
about this since you called
and there's nothing I can tell you
that I haven't already told the police.
Just go over it again. We'll see
if we come up with something.
Your Porsche was
stolen from your driveway?
Uh-huh.
The passenger-side door was broken
so I figure that's how the thief got in.
Do you know a guy
named Joe Ahern?
I don't think so.
Do you ever eat at a
restaurant called Plato's?
- It's about two blocks from your office.
- Yeah, yeah, a couple times. Why?
Well, Joe Ahern is
the bartender there.
Oh, well, I don't drink. See, so
I wouldn't have gone in the bar.
Sometimes when I work late, I
go there, get something to eat.
- It's Greek. It's pretty good.
- Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Maybe it's all
just a coincidence.
- What?
- Well, your car was stolen.
You eat at Plato's.
And Joe Ahern, the guy
accused of stealing your car?
He works at Plato's.
Yeah.
These people got me down pat.
- It's like they worked with me.
- It's possible.
No, the only guy I
ever worked with,
Gary Scott's doing 3
to 5 at Atlanta State.
That's amazing.
What?
In my life, I've
robbed 27 banks.
Only one time did I have someone
collect the money from the tellers.
It was when I robbed the Willow
Springs Bank six years ago.
How'd they know that?
You didn't go to trial
on that robbery, did you?
- No, we cut a deal.
- Ah.
Not a lot of press. Details of
the robbery wouldn't be known.
Only somebody who was in the
bank when you robbed it six years ago
would know what you did.
- Do you think?
- This will play out.
Just take a little time.
- Congratulations.
- For what?
Did you know that
Dynamo Rent-A-Car
has approximately 373
blue Chevy Luminas?
Did you find the car
we're looking for?
You sure have a way of taking
the fun out of my little successes.
Did you find the car?
- You really are in a bad mood.
- Did you find the car?
You know how they
walk around the car
and they check it for little dings
and little dents before you rent it?
And then they do the same
thing when you bring it back?
Matt said the car
hit a parking meter.
And on the day of the
robbery, only one blue Lumina
was returned with a new
scratch on the front bumper.
What is that?
Probably Matt.
Who rented it?
Phony license. Phony address.
If you move up the black 4, you can
take your red 5 and put it right there.
Wait a minute.
Matt,
this is my house. This is my property.
We don't throw the ball in the house.
Sorry.
You wanna throw
the ball, take it, uh...
- Take it outside.
- He can't go outside.
Yeah, they're trying
to kill him outside.
He may not be safe in the house.
Have you ever had a gun
pointed at you, Miss Stone?
Yeah. Used to happen all
the time when I was a cop.
- Then you know how scary it is.
- Yeah.
I was a nervous wreck
at work the next day.
I've never been
like that before.
I kept thinking someone was
gonna stick a gun in my face.
After about an hour,
I went to see Sarah.
She's the head teller.
I told her I have to leave.
I don't think I can work
as a teller anymore.
- It's gotta be tough.
- Yeah.
- Is that all?
- Well, no.
I'm sorry but I'm gonna have to
ask you about the robbery again.
We have a witness, a young
boy saw the robbers' faces
and he's absolutely sure that
neither one of them was Willie Roach.
- So it's his word against mine?
- Yeah.
That's why we'd like
you to think about it again.
- Maybe you made a mistake.
- No, I didn't make a mistake.
I saw his eyes. He
called me by name.
I'll never forget him.
The robbers have
already tried to kill the boy.
We've had to put him into hiding
which makes us think
that he's probably right.
Tried to kill him. I
mean, you're sure?
I mean, I could've
sworn it was him.
It would be terrible if I
accused the wrong man.
Why don't you think about it?
Thanks. I'll see myself out.
It must have been really scary
having that gun pointed at you.
Yeah.
We just wanna make sure
the wrong man doesn't go to jail.
I should be back in an hour.
All right, all
right, I'm coming.
- What's all this?
- It's my lunch.
I gave you lunch.
You gave me one hot
dog. I was still hungry.
You know, they have 24-hour
room service here. You ought to try it.
I had a shrimp cocktail, a
roast beef with mashed potatoes
and a chocolate sundae
with a cherry on top.
I'm going downstairs
and cut you off.
No room service, no
phone calls, no nothing.
You want something, you're
gonna have to pay for it.
I put you here for your safety,
not to have a good time
and break me in the process.
Don't you think
you're overreacting?
- Room service. Pick up.
- It's open.
Drop it! Drop it now!
I wanna see your hands
up there on the wall.
Not that hand, the other one.
Nice job.
- Those the guys?
- Those are the guys.
Dad, you should've
seen it. It was very cool.
When they knocked on
the door, I was very relaxed.
I went up to them,
I said, "It's open."
Then the cops busted down the door
and there they were with their guns.
If the police hadn't been there,
they were gonna shoot me.
I don't believe it. They
were gonna kill me.
Mr. Matlock's pretty smart
getting them to follow him like that.
He's gonna get
you out of here, Dad.
I owe you one, boy.
When this is over with, I'm gonna
take you anywhere you wanna go.
- Hawaii, California, Mexico.
- Cancun?
They got fine women
in Mexico, Matt.
Yeah, I brought the kid
down to see his father.
Yeah, I heard Ben
was Joe's lawyer.
I tell you though, I
was kind of surprised.
- Doesn't seem like his kind of case.
- What makes you say that?
Well, the guy's a bum.
Well, they say you stay in
this business long enough,
- you handle them all.
- Maybe you're right.
Hello, Becky.
You know, you only
made that one mistake.
The only time Willie Roach ever
had somebody collect the money
from the tellers was the
time he robbed your bank.
Well, that doesn't prove
anything. You have no evidence.
That's not what they tell me.
Besides, only somebody who had been
at that robbery would have known that.
And you were there,
weren't you, Becky?
You're the only one that still
works at the bank that was there.
Okay, we're out of here.
Bye.
Six cents.
Three of a kind beats two
pair. A full house beats...
I know. I know.
- I fold.
- Nothing. Not even a pair.
You know, I don't even
have to cheat to beat you.
Game is not
over until it's over.
In that case, you maybe
wanna play for more money?
- Hey, you guys.
- Oh, hey, Jerr.
Doc Holliday here
is hustling me.
Man, it's like taking
candy from a baby.
Don't get cocky, kid.
- Right.
- I... How's about 10 cents?
I call you.
You don't have to say, "I
call you." Just say "call."
Call.
- How many cards you want?
- Um, think I'll take two.
Two. Put them down
there. Deuce, down and dirty.
Dealer takes one.
Okay.
Let's go up, uh,
how about 17 cents?
I fold.
I told you I'd take
you to the cleaners.
Better man won. Go to bed.
All right. Well, anytime you
wanna play, just give me a call.
- Okay.
- All right. Good night.
Good night.
Sleep tight.
You had a full house. Why
didn't you stay in the game?
Oh, we had a deal.
When one of us won a
dollar, he would go to bed.
Say, uh, Jerr, wanna sit
down and play a hand?
No.
All right. Hey, I'm glad you're
here. I had to talk to you.
- About what?
- Well, I tracked down
the owner of that stolen Jaguar
that we found over at the chop shop.
Yeah.
Guy was out of the country.
Didn't even know his car was stolen.
- Does he know Joe Ahern?
- No, he doesn't.
But he has been to Plato's and
the passenger door was broken into.
So both the owners of the stolen cars
have been to where Joe Ahern works?
I got a sick feeling in
the pit of my stomach.
- Yeah.
- Poor kid.
Well, he's smart, I guess.
Streetwise. I don't know.
He's a good kid.
He's a thief.
You're a lawyer. Your
daughter's a lawyer.
His father is a thief.
What do you expect?
I suppose.
You're his role model.
He looks up to you.
You hear the way he talks to me?
Look, all I'm saying
is that he thinks
you're smart and he knows
that you're good at what you do.
And that's why he's so hell-bent
on you representing his dad.
Well, I'm not his dad. Ha, ha.
Dealing with a 12-year-old boy
day-to-day, especially that one...
Think we're actually
gonna find anything in here?
You never know.
Ah.
Mm.
Ew.
The owners of the Porsche
and Jaguar both went to Plato's.
- It's a coincidence.
- Maybe.
I found this under the dash
of that stolen Honda Prelude.
- Chewing gum?
- Yeah.
The police are
doing a DNA test on it
but you and I know
how it's gonna turn out.
It might be best if
you talk to the boy.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, son.
Dad, look at these hotels in
Cancun. They got everything there.
- I'm telling you.
- Sit down.
We can learn how to
go snorkeling with tanks.
Please, sit down.
Is something wrong?
I wanna thank you
for all you've done.
- Dad, you already did that.
- Let me speak, please.
You're not gonna
make this easy, are you?
Dad, what's wrong?
I wanna thank you
for believing in me.
You went out, you got Ben Matlock
and you convinced him to defend me.
A father couldn't ask
for more from a son.
There's just one problem.
I'm guilty, Matt.
But I thought you
said you didn't do it.
- I lied.
- You said we'd never lie to each other.
Maybe to other people,
but never to each other.
Matt, I'm a thief. I'm not somebody
you ought to be looking up to.
And I believed you when
you said you didn't do it.
I know.
I'm trying to tell
you I'm going to jail.
No, no, you're not. Ben
Matlock will get you off.
- No, he won't.
- Yes, he will.
I had an arrangement
with him. He'll get you off.
- I'm gonna talk to him right now.
- Listen to me.
Ben Matlock and I
have already talked.
Now, I'm going to jail,
Matt, for maybe two years.
There's one good thing
that can come out of all this.
I want you to learn
not to be like me.
I don't want you to be a thief.
I don't want you
to wind up in jail.
You're a good kid.
You can do better
than me. You hear me?
I don't want you
to go to jail, Dad.
I know.
How come you never
told me about your uncle?
I don't wanna stay at his house.
Your father says
he's a good guy.
Yeah, well, maybe,
but there's no fun.
He's always lecturing
me about junk,
telling me to go to bed early,
never lets me cut school.
I think I'd like him.
Yeah, how would you like
an old coot with glasses
staring at you all the time?
I don't know how to answer that.
Well, could be he
doesn't trust you.
You need to make him trust
you. Give you more freedom.
- And maybe hell will freeze over.
- Ha, ha.
How come I can't stay with you?
You wouldn't like it here.
It would be a lot
better than Uncle Bob.
I'm sorry, Matt, but I'm past getting
kids off to school and making lunches.
- Been there, done that, huh?
- Yep, yep.
But I tell you, if you wanna come hang
around some weekend, give me a call.
Deal.
www.tvsubtitles.net